John W. Warner papers MSS 10191
University of Virginia, Special Collections Dept.
- John Warner papers (-by accession), 1970-2007; MSS 10191_by; 713 Cubic Feet Cubic foot boxes; This collection consists of 712 cubic foot boxes.
  - National Business Aviation Association, NASA, Transportation, and Ship Scrapping (Conrad Schatte), 1/1/2000-12/31/2007 (Box 477)
    Rail: VRE (Virginia Railway Express)/Amtrak Insurance; Highways: I-64 Widening; Transportation: Auto-Right to Repair; Ship Scrapping: Ship Scrapping Tax Credit; Ship Scrapping: Ghost Fleet - Spiro's; NASA: NASA; Transit: Transit in Virginia 2000; Transit: Mort Zuckerman and Dulles Rail; Highways: Hampton Roads Transportation Issues; Rail: Bristol to DC; Ship Scrapping: Ghost Fleet - Local Governments; National Business Aviation Association (NBAA) [accordion folder]; NASA: NASA/Langley - Aerospace Grants; Rail: VRE (Virginia Railway Express); NASA: NASA Earth Science & Atmospheric, Langley - Goddard; Transit: METRO; Rail: Amtrak Veterans; Transit: West Group - Tyson's Tunnel, Proposal Data; Transportation: GMU UTC; Ship Scrapping: Commerce Committee Hearing; Rail: I-81; Rail: TRANSCAER Tour/NS/AAR 10/7/2002; Highways: Third-Crossing; Highways: Rockingham County Route 820; Ship Scrapping: EPW EPA Budget Hearing 2/26/2003; Ship Scrapping [accordion folder]; Highways: I-73; Transit: Hampton Roads; Ship Scrapping: Evergreen; Transit: Rail to Dulles; Highways: 19th Street Bridge; Highways: 2nd Access - Ft. Eustis; Highways: Norfolk Southern I-81 Plan; Highways: Traficland.com Northern Virginia Traffic; Transit: WMATA - Royal Street Garage; Ship Scrapping: MARAD Ship Scrapping; Transportation: MBTE - EPW; Transit: Letter to Governor Warner re: Dulles Rail; NASA: NASA - Aerospace; Transportation: DoT - Hours of Service NPRM; Transportation: General; Rail: RR 4.3 Tax Repeal; Ship Scrapping: USS Gage; NASA: Columbia Draft; Transportation: DHL License; Rail: Virginia Rail Plans 2003; Highways: Capitol Region Scenic Byways Request; Highways: Route 58; Transit: Transportation - Washington, DC Urbanized Area, Fredericksburg MPO Transit Issue; Ship Scrapping: Eckford/Isherwood (TAOS); NASA: Spaceport Tax Bill; Rail [accordion folder]; Ship Scrapping: Eckford/Isherwood; Rail: High Speed Rail; Highways: Route 460 Financial Feasibility Study; Highways: Smart Road - UPI; NASA: Space Grant
  - Appropriations, September 11 Energy Supplemental, Alcohol Labeling, and High Tech (Conrad Schatte), 1/1/2001-12/31/2006 (Box 478)
    High Tech: Information Security; High Tech: Senate Republican High Tech Caucus; High Tech: MCI Investigation, Collins (Government Affairs Committee), Chas Phillips, Alec Rodgers - Government Affairs; High Tech: VeriSign; Alcohol Labeling: BWXT; FY 2003 Omnibus Appropriations [accordion folder]; High Tech: AeA/AOL Meeting; FY 2003 Appropriations (Floor Activity): Drought; High Tech: CAPNET 7/14/2003; High Tech: Computer Professionals Clarification - FLSA; High Tech: Spectrum; High Tech: S. 88 Internet Tax Credits; September 11 Emergency Supplemental: CAPWIN; FY 2007 DHS Appropriations: JW - NCR Amendment; High Tech: HTTF Kick-Off 6/19/2003; FY 2003 Appropriations (Floor Activity): Dayton Expatriation SA 80; High Tech: Micron/Infineon; FY 2003 Appropriations (Floor Activity): Edwards/Lieberman NSR Amendment (SA 67); High Tech: UWB (Ultra Wide Band); September 11 Emergency Supplemental: Governor's Action; High Tech: EAA (Export Administration Act); High Tech: Xybernaut; High Tech: AOL-Time Warner; High Tech: MCI WorldCom; High Tech: NVTC (Northern Virginia Technology Council) Governor's Commission; FY 2003 Appropriations (Floor Activity): Amtrak Appropriations Letter FY 2003; High Tech: NVTC (Northern Virginia Technology Council) Fall Banquet; FY 2007 DHS Appropriations [accordion folder]; September 11 Emergency Supplemental: September 11 Appropriations Letters; FY 2003 Appropriations (Floor Activity): Omnibus Miscellaneous; High Tech: Privacy; High Tech: Internet Taxation; High Tech: E-58; FY 2007 DHS Appropriations: Menendez SA 4634 - Grants; September 11 Emergency Supplemental: Press Clips; High Tech: Auction 35 - FCC Letter; FY 2007 DHS Appropriations: Collins FEMA; High Tech: Napster; FY 2003 Appropriations (Floor Activity): Kennedy Education Amendment SA13; High Tech: Net Fair; FY 2003 Appropriations (Floor Activity): Letter to Loy on Transportation ID Cards 1/2003; FY 2003 Appropriations (Floor Activity): SA 1 (Byrd Omnibus) FY 2003 Appropriations; High Tech: EAA Spectrum; High Tech: DoD - Broadband; Alcohol Labeling: Ethanol & Corn Prices; High Tech: High-Tech Events; Alcohol Labeling [accordion folder]; High Tech: DoD - High Tech; High Tech: ICANN; FY 2003 Appropriations (Floor Activity): Harkin Burne Grants SA 32; FY 2003 Appropriations (Floor Activity): Schumer-Warner (Port Security Amendment); FY 2003 Appropriations (Floor Activity): Schumer Port Security SA 31; FY 2003 Appropriations (Floor Activity): Cochran Agriculture Emergency SA 204; High Tech: COMDEX; September 11 Emergency Supplemental: Reagan National
  - Appropriations: Commerce, Justice, Science, and Related Agencies, and Labor, Health and Human Services and Education, 1/1/2005-12/31/2005 (Box 479)
    FY 2006 CJS Requests: Suffolk; FY 2006 CJS Requests: Newport News; FY 2006 CJS Requests: Chesapeake Police Department (CAD); FY 2006 Labor HHS: Fairfax County Park Authority; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments; FY 2006 Labor HHS: VA Dental Association; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Council for America's First Freedom; FY 2006 Labor HHS: John Tyler CC (Chester); FY 2006 Labor HHS: Communities in Schools; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Occupational Enterprises Inc.; FY 2006 CJS Requests: VCPI (Virginia Community Policing Institute); FY 2006 Labor HHS: INOVA; FY 2006 CJS Requests: Regent University; FY 2006 Labor HHS: City of Norfolk; FY 2006 Labor HHS: VA State Court NCLB (No Child Left Behind; FY 2006 Labor HHS: VA Museum of Fine Arts; FY 2006 CJS Requests: Virginia Beach; FY 2006 Labor HHS: City of Portsmouth; FY 2006 CJS Requests: Fairfax (2005) Gang; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Eastern VA Medical School; FY 2006 Labor HHS: An Achievable Dream; FY 2006 Labor HHS: CHKD (Children's Hospital of the King's Daughters); FY 2006 Labor HHS: Bon Secours Richmond Community Hospital; FY 2006 CJS Requests: Achievable Dream (FY 2006) (Cameras); FY 2006 CJS Requests: Innovative Wireless Technologies; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Center for Excellence in Education; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Fairfax County Board of Supervisors; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Virginia Western CC/Central Virginia CC; FY 2006 CJS Requests: Miretek Systems; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Jamestown; FY 2006 Labor HHS: VA Aquarium and Marine Science Center; FY 2006 Labor HHS: UVA - Wise; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Alliance for Consumer Education; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Memorial Child Guidance Clinic; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Project Lifesaver; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Hoofbeats Therapeutic Riding Center; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Virginia Military Institute (VMI); FY 2006 CJS Requests: KidsPeace (FY 2006); FY 2006 Labor HHS: D-Day - Bedford; FY 2006 Labor HHS: William & Mary; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Riverside Health System; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Fredericksburg Area Museum & Cultural Center; FY 2006 Labor HHS: City of Suffolk; FY 2006 Labor HHS: UVA - Center for Politics; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Hollins University; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Best Buddies; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Virginia's Center for Innovative Technologies; FY 2006 Labor HHS: MediCorp Health System; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Piedmont Access to Health Services; FY 2006 Labor HHS: KidsSave; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Operation Smile; FY 2006 Labor HHS: National Maritime Heritage Foundation; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Southside CC Trucks; FY 2006 CJS Requests: Lonesome Pine; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Virginia High School League; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Wolf Trap; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Regent; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Ethiopian Community Center; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Hampton University; FY 2006 Labor HHS: VA Living Museum; FY 2006 Labor HHS: University of Appalachia; FY 2006 CJS Requests: Chesapeake Fire Department & EMS; FY 2006 CJS Requests: Portsmouth; FY 2006 CJS Requests: Virginia Community Criminal Justice Association; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Woodrow Wilson Presidential Library; FY 2006 CJS Requests: Norfolk; FY 2006 Labor HHS: J. S. Mosby Museum Foundation; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Jewish Family Services; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Child and Family Network; FY 2006 CJS Requests: Charlottesville Police (FY 2005); FY 2006 Labor HHS: Carilion Health System; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Patient Services Inc. (PSI); FY 2006 CJS Requests: William & Mary; FY 2006 Labor HHS: CNU (Christopher Newport University); FY 2006 CJS Requests: Fauquier County; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Shenandoah University; FY 2006 CJS Requests: CHKD (Children's Hospital of the King's Daughters) 2005; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Ruritan National, Inc.; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Virginia Tech; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Institute for Advanced Learning and Research; FY 2006 Labor HHS: GMU - Krasnow; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Levine School of Music; FY 2006 Labor HHS: Tech Access; FY 2006 CJS Requests: ChildSafeNet (Fairfax); FY 2006 Labor HHS: VCCS (Virginia Community College System); FY 2006 CJS Requests: ChildSave Memorial Child Guidance Clinic (FY 2006)
  - Supreme Court Nominations, and Security Clearance, Pardon, and Clemency Requests, 1/1/2004-12/31/2006 (Box 480)
    John Roberts Background: Statements of John Warner on John Roberts; Hogan & Hartson/Holland & Knight: Exhibits to Memorandum in Support of Petition for Absolute Pardon; Samuel A. Alito Jr.: National Council of Jewish Women [presentation folder]; John Roberts Background: Etc. ...Bork; Telart Tech; Samuel A. Alito Jr. [accordion folder]; Samuel A. Alito Jr.: Honorable Samuel A. Alito, Jr. Nominated to be Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States [binder]; John Roberts Background: Roberts Arguments Pro; John Roberts Background: Roberts Draft Statement; John Roberts Background: Short Statement; Hogan & Hartson/Holland & Knight: The Norfolk 4 A Case of Innocence [presentation folder]; Untitled Folder: D. Local Service Provider Worksheet; Samuel A. Alito Jr.: Supreme Court Nominee - Alliance for Justice [presentation folder]; John Roberts Background [accordion folder]; Hogan & Hartson/Holland & Knight: Memorandum in Support of Petition for Absolute Pardon; Pardon; John Roberts Background: Senator John Warner on Roberts; Samuel A. Alito Jr.: CWA - Confirm Judge Samuel Alito: Fair Hearing, Fair Process, Fair Up or Down Vote [presentation folder]; Samuel A. Alito Jr.: Statement of Opposition and Final Report for Nomination of Samuel Alito [spiralbound]; John Roberts Background: Senator John Warner #s on Advice and Consent; Levin Clemency; John Roberts Background: Long Statement
  - Hurricane Katrina Hearings (Conrad Schatte), 9/14/2005-3/30/2006 (Box 481)
    Effects of Earthquakes, Fault Movements, and Subsidence on the South Louisiana Landscape [report]; EPW Katrina Hearing 11/1/2005 [binder]; Untitled Presentation Folder: Hurricane Katrina: Why Did the Levees Fail? 11/2/2005; Hurricane Katrina: Search & Rescue - Hearing 1/30/2006 [binder]; Hurricane Katrina: Coast Guard - Hearing 11/9/2005 [binder]; Hurricane Katrina Hearing 10/6/2005 [binder]; Hurricane Katrina Hearing 10/20/2005 [binder]; Evacuating New Orleans - Hearing 1/31/2006 [binder]; Hurricane Katrina: FEMA - Hearing 12/8/2005 [binder]; Hurricane Katrina: Levees #2 - Hearing - 12/15/2005 [binder]; Hurricane Katrina: Private Sector - Hearing 11/16/2005 [binder]; Performance Reviews of FEMA's Disaster Management Activities in Response to Hurricane Katrina, 3/2006 [book]; Loose Papers: Testimony on the Failure of the Gulf Coast Levees During Hurricane Katrina 11/16/2005-11/17/2005; Effects of Geological Faults on Levee Failures in South Louisiana [spiralbound]; Hurricane Katrina Hearing 9/14/2005 [binder]; Hurricane Pam Exercise - Hearing 1/24/2006 [binder]; Hurricane Katrina Hearing 9/28/2005 [binder]
  - Hurricane Katrina Hearings (Conrad Schatte), 1/31/2006-2/10/2006 (Box 482)
    Exhibit Book - Hurricane Katrina: The Role of Governors in Managing the Catastrophe 2/2/2006 Committee on Homeland Security and Government Affairs [binder]; Managing New Orleans - Hearing 2/1/2006 [binder]; Hurricane Katrina: Role of Governors - Hearing 2/2/2006 [binder]; Hurricane Katrina: DHS & FEMA Leaders - Hearing 2/10/2006 [binder]; Exhibit Book - Hurricane Katrina: Managing Law Enforcement and Communications in a Catastrophe, Committee on Homeland Security and Government Affairs, 2/6/2006 [binder]; Exhibit Book - Hurricane Katrina: Managing the Crisis and Evacuating New Orleans 2/1/2006 Committee on Homeland Security and Government Affairs [binder]; Exhibit Book - Challenges in a Catastrophe: Evacuating New Orleans in Advance of Hurricane Katrina 1/31/2006 Committee on Homeland Security and Government Affairs [binder]
  - Appropriations, Armed Services, Agriculture, Nutrition, and Forestry, Aging, and Administration Committees for the 108th Congress, 1/1/2003-12/31/2004 (Box 483)
    108th Appropriations - Cosigned Letters (2 accordion folders); 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2004): Defense; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2004): VA - HUD; 108th Armed Services [accordion folder]; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2004): Commerce; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2004): Agriculture; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2005): Military Construction; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2004): Military Construction; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2004): Labor - HHS; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2005): Legislative Branch; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2004): General Appropriations; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2005): Homeland Security; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2005): Foreign Operations; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2005): CJS; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2005): DC; 108th Administration [accordion folder]; 108th Agriculture, Nutrition, and Forestry [accordion folder]; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2004): Transportation; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2004): Interior; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2005): Transportation; 108th Aging [accordion folder]; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2005): Defense; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2005): Energy; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2004): Energy and Water; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2005): Agriculture; 108th Appropriations [accordion folder]; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2005): Labor, HHS; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2004): DC; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2004): Homeland Security; 108th Appropriations Request (FY 2005): VA - HUD
  - Defense Projects and Appropriations Requests (Cord Sterling and Jim Kadtke), 1/1/2004-12/31/2005 (Box 484)
    FY 2006 Press Releases; Madison Associates, LLC: Cord Sterling [presentation folder]; Aurora Golden-Eye UAV FY 2006 Request; Allied Aerospace UAV; Intermec [presentation folder]; Lessons Learned; Foreign Operations Appropriations Letter; James Madison University: Senator John Warner [presentation folder]; Madison Associates, LLC: Conrad Schatte and Jim Kadtke [presentation folder]; Narricot Industries, LP, OTV Meeting, 7/26/2005 [packet]; Foreign Operations Appropriations; FY 2006 Request Documents; "Developing Leaders Who Can Lead Change" Education for Transformation Brief to Dr. Jim Kadtke, John J. Garstka, Office of Force Transformation, OSD, 2/11/2005 [binder]; FY 2006 Foreign Operations Appropriations Material; Untitled Folder: Nanomaterials, Materials Modification Inc.; FY 2006 Budget Roll-Outs; Untitled Folder: Raytheon, 2005; Senator John Warner FY 2006 Sac-D Request Letter; Iraq Project - W & M Project; GH: Argon; Darrell Campbell; Jim Kadtke; Senator John Warner Tuesday 2/8, 11:30 am [presentation folder]; Handwriting Documentation; Progeny Systems: Engineering Solutions That Last Generations [presentation folder]; Star Technologies 2006 Appropriations Defense Request; GLS: LOGOS; Greg Poe; Jim Kadtke - Senator John Warner, Wednesday 3/2, 11:00 am [presentation folder]; NMLC Automated Information Technology; For Conference; JADOCS: SAIC Virtual Training Issue; Intermec FY 2006 SNTS (Navy Serial Number Tracking System) & POMX/CAS (Air Force Point of Maintenance/Combat Ammunition System); Aurora FY 2006 Excalibur Request; SureTrak Integrated Track Management System [packet]; Executive Summary; Madison Associates, LLC: Elaine McCusker [presentation folder]; Untitled Folder: Senator John Warner's FY 2006 Defense Appropriations; Fluid Tran Inc. [presentation folder]; Automated Manifest System - Tactical (AMS-TAC) [packet]; Loose Papers: Defense Technology, 2004-2005; Defense Life Seminars; Thorium; BSEI; Amendments
  - Appropriations Requests: Transportation, Energy, and Environment (Tack Richardson), 1/1/2005-12/31/2005 (Box 485)
    Hampton Roads Transit (HRT); Transportation: Route 29 & Gallows Road Intersection Improvements: County of Fairfax [accordion folder]; Chesapeake Bay Requests; Transportation: Route 17 Dominion Boulevard: City of Chesapeake [accordion folder]; Transportation: VRE Two Tier Locomotive: Virginia Railway Express [accordion folder]; VA HUD: Invasive Species Regional Education: Fairfax Water [accordion folder]; Transportation: USMC Heritage Center Interchange: Prince William [accordion folder]; TEA-21 Earmarks Requests (Banking) [accordion folder]; Transportation: Stafford County Airport: Stafford County; Transportation: Dismal Swamp Trail: Interior; General Appropriations Information [accordion folder]; Transportation: Siesta Gardens Alternate Access Road: City of Portsmouth [accordion folder]; VA HUD: Allegheny/Grayson County Water Supply: Allegheny/Grayson County [accordion folder]; Assorted Transportation Appropriations; Energy and Water Information [accordion folder]; VA HUD: Water Environment Research Foundation: Alexandria Sanitation Authority [accordion folder]; VA HUD: Occoquan Watershed Land Protection: Fairfax Water [accordion folder]; Village of Oyster Ecosystem: The Nature Conservancy (Energy and Water) [accordion folder]; TEA-21 Earmarks (EPW-Highway) [accordion folder]; Transportation Appropriations; Transportation: Richmond Highway Transportation Initiative: County of Fairfax [accordion folder]; VA HUD: Shenandoah Valley Discovery Museum [accordion folder]; VA HUD: Water/Wastewater Infrastructure Project: City of Norfolk [accordion folder]; VA HUD: Southeast Section Sanitary Sewer: Newport News [accordion folder]; VA HUD: Atlee Manor/Sharon Park Septic Tanks: Hanover County [accordion folder]; Transportation: Virginia Smart Road: Virginia Tech [accordion folder]
  - Appropriations Requests: Transportation and Interior (Tack Richardson), 1/1/2005-12/31/2005 (Box 486)
    Transportation: Petersburg Transit Intermodal Facility: Petersburg Area Transit Co. [accordion folder]; Interior: Shenandoah Valley Battlefields: SVB Foundation [accordion folder]; Transportation: Commonwealth Highway-Marine Intermodal: The Commonwealth Railway [accordion folder]; Transportation: Fairfax County Parkway & Fair Lakes Parkway Interchange: County of Fairfax [accordion folder]; Transportation: Product Development Center: Virginia Tech [accordion folder]; Transportation: Hampton Roads Transit Bus Facility: HRT [accordion folder]; Interior: Occoquan National Wildlife Refuge: Friends of Potomac River Refuges [accordion folder]; Interior: Dismal Swamp Visitor's Center: City of Chesapeake [accordion folder]; Transportation: Elizabeth River Intermodal Facility: City of Norfolk [accordion folder]; Interior: Eastern Shore of VA NWR: The Nature Conservancy [accordion folder]; Transportation: Bus Operations & Maintenance Facility: Greater Richmond Transit [accordion folder]; Interior: Fisherville Wastewater Treatment Plant: Augusta County [accordion folder]; Transportation: Fairfax County Parkway HOV Lane to Dulles: County of Fairfax [accordion folder]; New River Corridor: New River Land Trust; Transportation: Potomac Center Community Parking Facility: Potomac Center Limited Partners [accordion folder]; Interior: Dragon Run: The Nature Conservancy [accordion folder]; Transportation: Fort Eustis Gateway Corridor: Newport News [accordion folder]; Transportation: Greater Lynchburg Transit Company Vehicle Replacement: GLTC [accordion folder]; Interior: Federal Conservation Efforts (Landowner Incentive Program): NatureServe [accordion folder]; Interior: Visitor's Center at Fredericksburg/Spotsylvania Battlefields: Fredericksburg Regional Chamber of Commerce [accordion folder]; Transportation: GMU Intelligent Transportation: GMU [accordion folder]; Transportation: Isle of Wight: Emergency Signals: Isle of Wight [accordion folder]; Transportation: PRTC Buses: Prince William [accordion folder]; Interior: The Cove Project: Ward Burton Foundation [accordion folder]; Interior: Center for Advanced Separation: Virginia Tech [accordion folder]; Transportation: Isle of Wight: Bridge Warning: Isle of Wight [accordion folder]; Interior: Martin Luther King National Memorial: MLK, Jr. National Memorial Foundation [accordion folder]; Interior: Back Bay NWR Expansion: Friends of Back Bay [accordion folder]; Transportation: Newport News Williamsburg Baggage Claim Upgrade: Newport News/Williamsburg Airport [accordion folder]; Transportation: Blacksburg Transit Intermodal Facility: Blacksburg Transit [accordion folder]; Transportation: Center for Excellence in Surface Transportation Safety: Virginia Tech [accordion folder]; Transportation: Gainesville - Haymarket Extension of VRE: Virginia Railway Express [accordion folder]; Transportation: I-66/Route 29 Interchange: Prince William [accordion folder]; Transportation: I-66/Vienna Metrorail Accessibility: County of Fairfax [accordion folder]; Transportation: Colonial Parkway Ticketing: Jamestown [accordion folder]; Interior: Char-Lo Timberland Land Acquisition: Char-Lo Timberland and Trust for Public Land [accordion folder]; Interior: Project Alpha & Saving Grace: Lee County & Lincoln Preservation Trust [accordion folder]; Transportation: Dismal Swamp Trail: City of Chesapeake [accordion folder]; Interior: Onancock Sewage Treatment: Town of Onancock [accordion folder]
  - Appropriations Requests: Commerce, Justice, Science, and Related Agencies, Energy and Water, Department of Homeland Security, and Defense (Tack Richardson), 1/1/2005-12/31/2005 (Box 487)